const qBank = [
	{
		id: 1,
		question: "If Kara earns $80 in 8 hours, how many hours will it take her to earn $500?",
		options: ["40 hours", "50 hours", "500 hours", "250 hours"],
		answer: "500 hours",
	},
	{
		id: 2,
		question: " What fraction of a millimeter is a nanometer?",
		options: ["One thousandth", "One millionth", "One hundredth", "One ten thousandth"],
		answer: "One millionth",
	},
	{
		id: 3,
		question: "Who is considered the father of Mathematics?",
		options: ["Pythagorus", "Euclid", "Lao Tzu", "Albert Einstein"],
		answer: "Pythagorus"
	},
	{
		id: 4,
		question: "What is the name for the longest side of a right-angled triangle?",
		options: ["Hypothesis", " Hypotenuse", "Hypocrite", "Hypocrite"],
		answer: " Hypotenuse"
	},
	{
		id: 5,
		question: "How many hours are there in a week?",
		options: ["60", "24", "168", "2400"],
		answer: "168"
	},
	{
		id: 6,
		question: "The basic shape of the North American continent on a map is best described as which?",
		options: ["Square", "Triangular", "Hexagonal", "Circular"],
		answer: "Triangular"
	},
    {
		id: 7,
		question: "With which branch of mathematics is Euclid chiefly associated?",
		options: ["Trigonometry", "Calculus", " Probability", "Geometry"],
		answer: "Geometry"
	},
	
	{
		id: 8,
		question: "The angles of a triangle are in the ratio 1: 2: 3. The greatest angle will be",
		options: ["60°", "180°",  "90°", "360°"],
		answer: "90°"
	},
	{
		id: 9,
		question: "What shape are honeycomb cells?",
		options: ["Triangles", "Pentagons", "Squares", "Hexagons"],
		answer: "Hexagons"
	},
	{
		id: 10,
		question: "What is a natural number called if it has exactly two distinct divisors?",
		options: ["Integer", "Prime number", "Composite number", "Perfect number"],
		answer: "Prime number"
	},
	{
		id: 11,
		question: "Which of these numbers is not a square?",
		options: ["169", "186", "100", "225"],
		answer: "186"
	},
	{
		id: 12,
		question: " If + means ÷, ÷ means –, – means x and x means +, then: 9 + 3 ÷ 5 - 3 x 7 = ?",
		options: ["15", "5", "25", "None of the above"],
		answer: "None of the above"
	},
	{
		id: 13,
		question: "All natural numbers and 0 are called the _______ numbers.",
		options: ["Whole", "Prime", "Integer", "Rational"],
		answer: "Whole"
	},
	{
		id: 14,
		question: "The product of 121 x 10 x 200 x 0 X 25 is",
		options: ["121000", "22500", "9900", "None of the above"],
		answer: "None of the above"
	},
	{
		id: 15,
		question: "What is the value of cos 90? ",
		options: ["0", "1", "undefined", "1/2"],
		answer: "0"
	},
	{
		id: 16,
		question: "A palindromic number is a number that is the same when written ____.",
		options: ["1 and 2", "10 and 20", "Forwards or backward", "None of the above"],
		answer: "Forwards or backward"
	},
	{
		id: 17,
		question: "Amongst which of the following symbol is known as the product symbol?",
		options: ["Σ", "∏", "ε", "π"],
		answer: "∏"
	},
	{
		id: 18,
		question: "What is the formula to find the volume of a cone?",
		options: ["(1 / 3 )πrh", "(1 / 3 )πr²h", "(1 / 3 )πr1/2h", "None of the above"],
		answer: "(1 / 3 )πr²h"
	},
	{
		id: 19,
		question: "What is the derivative of f(x) = 100?",
		options: ["0", "1", "∞", "-∞"],
		answer: "0"
	},
	{
		id: 20,
		question: "In a triangle, the sum of the interior and exterior angles is ____?",
		options: ["Supplementary", "Complimentary", "Vertical", "None of the above"],
		answer: "Supplementary"
	},
	{
		id: 21,
		question: "____ is the distance calculated across the center between any two places on the circumference.",
		options: ["Radius", "Circumference", "Area", "Diameter"],
		answer: "Diameter"
	},
	{
		id: 22,
		question: " How do you write 90 in a Roman number?",
		options: ["C", "CX", "XC", "XXC"],
		answer: "XC"
	},
	{
		id: 23,
		question: "Which of the following is a Fibonacci series formula?",
		options: ["Fn = Fn+1 - Fn+2", "Fn = Fn-1 * Fn-2", "Fn = Fn+1 + Fn-2", "Fn = Fn-1 + Fn-2"],
		answer: "Fn = Fn-1 + Fn-2"
	},
	{
		id: 24,
		question: " Evaluate (2*5)^3?",
		options: ["100", "30", "250", "1000"],
		answer: "1000"
	},
	{
		id: 25,
		question: "Evaluate x^2 * x^6?",
		options: ["x^12", "x^8", "x^-4", "None of the above"],
		answer: "x^8"
	},
]

export default qBank;
